Hello everyone! We are
Miericorchoy!
Today, all the members came to visit our current collaborator
We all came to visit Sweets Productions, with whom we are currently collaborating!
Thank you very much!
They have made a lot of really nice menus and goods for us.
We hope everyone enjoys Sweets Productions today!
Thank you very much!
By the way, before this collaboration menu was completed
We had a tasting party with the members before the collaboration menu was completed.
Did any of the members participate?
Yes!
How was it? How was it?
It was really delicious!
What?
It was amazing!
It was so good, I lost my vocabulary.
It was really good, wasn't it?
You know, you've already seen the pictures, right?
You've already seen the pictures of my menu.
But when you make the real thing
I feel like I really want to take a picture of it!
Ehhhh...
That's amazing.
It shows your personality, doesn't it?
Yeah.
So, how was it, Aimi?
I was able to eat my own menu.
I was able to eat my own menu, but I also tried the menus of Ai and Ai's Lennon.
I was really impressed by how delicious it was.
It was amazing!
I'm looking forward to it!
Now let's sit down and eat from the collaboration menu that was prepared for us!
Bon appétit!
Yes, the menu I have come up with is
Umamama Cheesy Hamburger Steak!
Looks delicious!
It looks like a heart! Be a heart.
Yes, it's a heart.
I love cheeseburgers.
It looks so delicious with the Joy symbol on the cheese!
So cute!
It's cute, and it's got a fried egg on it.
Please try the Cheesy Hamburger and be Julie!
Please be Julie!
And I've been thinking about this one.
Connor's Yukubari Sweet Potato Parfait!
Looks delicious!
My penlight colors are light purple and yellow
The colors of my penlight are light purple and yellow, which are the colors of sweet potatoes.
So I used sweet potatoes!
Delicious!
And it's not pudding?
The logo is a monaka, and it's very cute!
I hope you all enjoy it!
I like that it doesn't melt.
It's so cute!
Here you go.
I smashed it.
Here's what's on my menu.
Concalbleurre.
It's the same as Conner's, but it's a Nuari Korju Monaca.
It's pink and cute!
Thank you so much!
And I love that it comes with fruit.
That's right.
Not only do we have Brulee, but we have fruit as well, so please try it!
Eggsugi set meal!
It comes with 4 small nests!
It's a set meal, so it's enough to fill you up.
And it's all eggs!
It's also good for those who are trying to build up their protein and muscle mass!
Thank you very much.
It's well-balanced.
You're doing a great job.You seem nice.
Bon appétit!
It's a little bit of cheese, a little bit of diet.
Today's presentation is also very pretty cheese.
What's going on? What's going on?
I wonder how it's printed.
That's for sure.
Bon appétit.
Here you go.
I like it.
It's on the level.
Cheese is delicious
Delicious.
Oh, my God.
Oh, wow.
That's nice.
It's good.
You should try it.
Well, I'll try it.
Hey.
I'll just leave it here.
Looks so good.
Yum! Yum!
Looks delicious.
Mmm.
So sweet potato!
Oh, sweet potato cream!
Sweet potato cream!
Oh, no!
Wait a minute... he really ate this!
I want some!
And please eat it.
There's actually a whole pudding in here.
Gentlemen!
I love the pudding!
The sesame seeds really match the sweet potatoes.
It's like a sweet potato and a sweet potato.
It's really like a college sweet potato. Eh, really like a college potato
Onira flavor
Please try it!
I love it!
Eat it!
Bon appétit!
Bon appétit. - Bon appétit. - Bon appétit.
Oh, wow.
This toro.
This is toro.
This is definitely delicious.
Looks delicious!
Bon appétit!
Here you go.
How is it?
It's good.
Yummy?
It's so good.
Sweet.
Yummy?
Good.
Delicious.
Breakfast
Okay, what's on the menu for me?
One sip of banana juice and you'll be smiling and happy.
Yay!
My stomach is something else.
I can serve myself!
Oh, my gosh!
That's great.
This is because I personally like banana juice.
yellow, which is the group's color.
I also made the banana juice with the light yellow of my open night color in mind.
It's perfect!
Please eat and drink as much as you can! Please eat and drink a lot.
That's good.
And you, Mai?
Yes, I'll have this one.
I'll have a colorful soda.
It's good.
It's kind of good.
Everyone has come up with so many ideas for the menu.
I thought it would be a refreshing drink.
By all means.
I hope you'll drink a lot of it!
I heard that each one tastes different.
Yes, each one is different.
Yes.
By all means.
Please enjoy drinking them one by one.
Looks delicious.
Here's what I've come up with for the menu.
Mr. Blue's Melon Soda Kumatan Sif!
Here's the important part!
Kumadan Sifu's best drink!
It's really cute!
It's cute, isn't it?
Let me try this.
Oh, wow.
There's a wolf.
It's so cute.
It's adorable.
So cute.
Please drink this and have a meltdown with Mr. Blue and Miyagi!
I'm looking forward to working with you.
So cute!
Here's my menu item, Miso Ramen with Miso and More Love from Micchan!
I feel like I'm in a ramen shop! Even though I'm in Sweets Paradise, I can eat ramen like this!
I feel like I'm at a ramen shop, even though I'm at Sweets Paradise!
In my opinion, it would be even more delicious if you dip it in the soup after eating all of the ramen!In my opinion, it would be even better if you dip it in the soup after you finish it all!
I hope you will try it too!
The eggs look delicious!
Micchan's face is awesome!
The aroma
It smells so good!
I'm hungry!
I'll have some of your vermicelli. Bon appétit.
Delicious! Delicious!
It smells so good! Oh, I'm so glad I got the tube sailor!
Delicious!
So many ingredients!
It's so delicious!
The noodles are really filling too!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Ya-bah, this is the ramen that will make all ramen lovers swoon!
It will make your mouth water!
The waistline is so rich!
It really is!
I was allowed to drink it once at a tasting, so I'll take it as a saisai.
I wonder if it's Niko-niko.
I wonder if it makes me smile.
I'm not smiling at all.
Nico nico nico.
It's cute.
I'm working on it, Julie.
It's really good.
I'm glad you like it.
I'm so happy to be able to drink again.
Is this Ao's menu?
Yes, a melon mellow soda for you, Kumotanshi's best drink. Yes, a melon melon soda for Ao, with Kumotanshi's best shot.
Here you go.
Too cute!
Go ahead, take it.
It's too cute to waste, but I'll have it.
How is it?
It's really good.
It's so cute!
Even when it's melted, it still looks cute, like a bear taking a half-bath.
That's true.
It's so cute!
It really does taste... delicious.
I really want to drink it.
I'm so in love with Ao, aren't I?
The second one is a colorful soda that makes you fall in love with it.
So cute!
Looks delicious!
I heard it tastes different depending on the color...
I'll have a small piece of the soda.
Really, about 3 pieces have different tastes!
Delicious!
What do you think?
What is it?
That's it!
It tastes like Blue Hawaii.
Cider?
I don't know.
I don't know, but it's really good!
Please drink it!
Yes, please!
The menu I invented is called “Sweet Aloo Thai Milk Tea”!
I love it!
I love Thailand, but... I like Thailand, but I also like tapioca.
I also like tapioca, so I had Thai milk tea with tapioca.
And a lot of whipped cream, like this!
And I'll have this too.
Where do you put it?
I'm going to put it right here.
That's nice.
Pop it here.
Even without the color.
It's cute.
Absolutely delicious.
What is arroyo?
Aloi is a Thai word meaning delicious!
Please have a cup of sweet and tasty Thai milk tea!
I'd love it.
Yes, please!
I've come up with Yuka's Matcha Sweet Tea Latte.
I love matcha so much that I do it in many places.
I love matcha so much that I do it in so many places!
I'm very happy!
That's beautiful!
It's mine.
Put this on your stomach.
It's my brain.
I don't know...
Wow! Gray!
I'm having matcha green tea thicker and thicker.
I'm so happy.
That's beautiful!
I'd like to put it in the middle.
Wow!
It's very solid too.
It looks like a logo.
It looks like an icon.
Even from above, you can see the reflection of this.
It's like this.Certainly this way and this way.
eh?
I think I can do it.
I like it.
It looks so delicious!
Thank you very much.
I hope you all enjoy it!
Yes, my menu is Peach Peel Strawberry Milk with lots of love!
Just like me, it's very high in sugar, so please be careful not to get sick to your stomach!
Also, as I mentioned over there, I've actually mixed a little bit of love and a little bit of strawberry milk.
I'm not sure if anyone who drinks this will fall in love with me, but please be careful.
Please be careful.
Please drink a lot!
I also have this monaca on me, so please put it anywhere you like and take lots of pictures!
Thank you very much!
So cute!
The menu item I came up with is “Joy Potatoes”, which are my favorite french fries.
They are my favorite french fries, but they are also filled with fried bean curd, making them a very filling dish.
If you're not sure what to order, try Joy Potatoes!
By the way, what sauce is this?
The honey mustard one is ketchup, but you can put whatever you like on it and eat it!
It's absolutely delicious!
Please sign for it.
Okay, I'll eat it quickly! Rico first!
Oh, papioca!
It's so good!
It's so sweet! It's like...
It's not your average milk tea, it's a deep milk tea.
It's got a little bit of tea in it.
I love it!
It's so good! It's so good!
It's so good! It's so good! It's Thai!
It's Thai! It's delicious! It's so good to eat!
Please eat and drink.
This is amazing!
I was really close to it just now.
It smells like green tea! It smells like green tea!
It's so good! Looks good.
I'll drink it then.
Bon appétit.
Is it good?
It's so much green tea.
Here it is!
The person who drinks this must say this.
I love the taste of matcha.
That's exactly what it tastes like.
It's delicious.
I'm glad.
Want some? Alice.
Yes, I'll have the joy cocktail toast, please.
Yes!
Yes?
Basil!
Basil flavor!
They're absolutely delicious!
It's so cute!
I'll have the fancy flavor, please.
I love basil!
I'll have the honey mustard.
Looks delicious!
Delicious!
Another totally different taste!
Delicious honey mustard
Heavy honey mustard.
Stable.
Minuten Pool
4 died
Movie What?
Oh, how is it so bad?
I'm really looking forward to it!
Great!
I'll have a drink at the end with Momosamo!
I'll have a drink! I'll drink it.
Oh, my God.
I love the pink.
It looks great.
It's pretty.
Oh, I'm drinking.
Oh, really?
It's delicious.
Is it good?
It's my favorite flavor.
It's my favorite.
I want everyone to have a taste of my favorite flavor.
You should try it.
And this sauce?
It's like a color spray.
Yeah.
It's colorful.
I don't know.
It's nice.
She's happy.
I made it, didn't I?
I did.
Yeah, you did.
I'm awesome.
This isn't it.
You should try it.
Everybody loves our milk.
It's good.
It's delicious.
Yes, from here I'll introduce you to our collaboration goods.
Okay, Yuka, please.
Yes, I have two items now, a badge and a sticker!
So cute!
The back of the badge is really cute, and it has the joy color yellow on it, which really pops.
The size of the sticker is the size that can be seen on cell phones nowadays, so it's very cute!
You have already seen all the members' eyes before, so please pay attention to them.
I would like to introduce Acrica.
I'm in the 12th place in front of you, and it's so cute! I'm in the 12th place in front of you right now, and it's amazing to see them all side by side.
Onstarf
It's so cute that everyone wants to complete the collection.
The logo on the back is also very cute.
The logo on the back is also very cute, but it's three-dimensional, and so is everyone else's.
Seipala's
This is Seipala's SECCO.
Please get this Seypara's Sekko!
Rare, rare, rare!
Please get it!
The way it pops out is cute, isn't it?
So cute!
Please get the complete set that everyone wants!
Please!
In addition to the sale of goods, we are also holding a campaign to give away our solo panels.
We are also holding a panel present campaign where you can win our solo panels!
Wow!
I'm so happy!
You can apply for it by using the cafe, so we are looking forward to seeing you there!
Thank you very much.
So, once again, we are all here at Seichi Paradise today!
How was it?
Well, it was really great to be able to eat and drink the collaboration food and drinks that everyone put their hearts and souls into.
I was really happy to be able to eat and drink the collaboration food and drinks that everyone put their heart and soul into, and it was delicious!
It was delicious!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
It was a very exciting and fun collaboration drink!
We have a collaboration café, so if you would like to show this video, please come to the store!
Thank you very much!
That's all for now.
Bye bye!
See you soon.
Bye-bye.Bye-bye.
We'll be waiting for you.